goldeneaglecoin.com 2019-12-23

# Privacy-Policy | Golden Eagle Coins

#### Your Privacy

Golden Eagle Coins is committed to protecting your privacy. We only use the information we collect about you to process applications and to provide support to our members. Please read on for more details about our privacy policy.

#### What information do we collect? How do we use it?

When you place an order, we need to know your full name, email address, phone number, street address, credit card number, expiration date & security code.

#### How do we protect your information?

This site is hosted on a secured, dedicated server that does not allow access to the public. Firewalls passwords, and encryption technology (SSL) protect the information about our members we collect and store. 

#### What about "cookies"?

"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. We do not place any cookies on your computer or record any information about our visitors other than anonymous technical data used for statstical purposes only.

#### Will Golden Eagle Coins disclose the information it collects to outside parties?

Golden Eagle Coins does not sell, trade, rent or publish your personal information to any third party. Golden Eagle Coins may provide anonymous aggregate statistics about our members, site traffic patterns, and related site information to reputable third-parties, but these statistics will not include personally identifying information.

Golden Eagle Coins may release member information when we believe, in good faith, that such release is reasonably necessary to (i) comply with law, (ii) enforce or apply the terms of any of our member agreements or (iii) protect the rights, property or safety of Golden Eagle Coins our members, or others.

#### In Summary

Golden Eagle Coins is committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect on the site to assist and promote our members. We do not sell, trade, rent or publish any personal information.

**Your Consent**

By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of this anonymous information by Golden Eagle Coins. If we make any changes to our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

When you register with or make purchases from Golden Eagle Coins, we may occasionally send you emails containing special offers or information about new services and products. If you no longer wish to receive these emails, simply click UNSUBSCRIBE or send an email message to remove@goldeneaglecoin.com with "remove" in the subject line and your address will be deleted from our active mailing list.

#### Mailing List & Opt-Out Features

When you register with or make purchases from Golden Eagle Coins, we may occasionally send you emails containing special offers or information about new services and products. If you no longer wish to receive these emails, simply click [UNSUBSCRIBE](mailto:remove@goldeneaglecoin.com) or send an email message to remove@goldeneaglecoin.com with "remove" in the subject line and your address will be deleted from our active mailing list.

#### Questions and Feedback

If you have any questions or feedback related to our Privacy Policy, please email us at info@goldeneaglecoin.com .

Thank you for visiting Golden Eagle Coins!

Our Address:

Golden Eagle Coins  
3386 Fort Meade Rd  
Laurel MD 20724

800-735-1311
